pricequotes.com 2011-01-26

# PriceQuotes.com - Privacy Policy

Terms and Conditions of Use and Privacy Policy

**PriceQuotes.com** respects the privacy rights of its online visitors and is committed to providing a secure environment for them. To demonstrate our commitment, we have adopted an Online Privacy Policy that governs the information collection practices of our Web site.

Please note, however, that this policy applies only to sites maintained by PriceQuotes.com, and not to web sites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link. When you click-through to any other sites from the PriceQuotes.com Web site, this Privacy Policy no longer applies, since PriceQuotes.com does not control the privacy activities of those sites.

You, the user, agree that your use of the web site is subject to the following Terms and Conditions, which may be modified at any time. Continued access to the site by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Agreement. **If you do not agree with the Terms and Conditions, please do not use this site.**

**What information does PriceQuotes.com collect and how is it used?**

As an online referral service, PriceQuotes.com collects personally identifiable information from visitors who voluntarily opt-in to submit forms requesting free price quotes and estimates. This information can include zip codes, and, in certain instances, name, address, telephone and email information that is stored and used for the purposes of directing requests to established, pre-screened third party business partners who are directly able to fulfill the requests. Please note that we may send you follow-up communications related to the products, services or information you have requested from us.

From time to time, PriceQuotes.com may also collect and temporarily store personal information that visitors voluntarily submit to us via email correspondence. For example, PriceQuotes.com provides a link through which an online visitor can send email to Support. Any personal information contained in such email is used by PriceQuotes.com for the sole purpose of responding to your questions and/or comments and is deleted immediately after we've responded. Regardless of whether we've successfully responded, any personal information submitted to us in email is deleted within 30 days of its receipt.

In addition, we only collect and use personal information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to appropriately respond to your estimate-request, or emailed question and/or comment. Please note that your refusal to provide personal information (e.g., name, address, etc.) in an estimate-request or email correspondence may limit our ability to respond to your request, question or comment in a timely fashion. However, you never have to provide personal information to PriceQuotes.com in order to use our Web site.

**Log Files**

Other information collected by PriceQuotes.com is in the form of log files that record Web site activity, including how many "hits" a particular Web page is getting (a.k.a. "click-through data"). For example, log file entries are generated every time a visitor clicks "Get Price Quote" or "Submit to request a free in-home estimate" on our site. These entries are generated anonymously, and enable PriceQuotes.com to assess overall site activity, track interest in advertised sales, and troubleshoot technical concerns. We also use the log file entries for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the referral services we provide you. Log files are used internally only, and are not associated with any particular user, computer or browser. 

**Third Parties**

Through the use of frames, PriceQuotes.com also allows visitors to submit information requests about cars, automobile warranties, insurance, and hotel reservations to identified third party websites. For example, a visitor can submit information about a car's make, model and year to request a price quote. In addition, once a visitor has clicked for a price quote, the visitor may be asked to supply additional information, including personally identifiable information (e.g., name, address and telephone number). Please be aware, however, that information collected by identified third parties is not simultaneously collected or used by PriceQuotes.com; the information is collected and used exclusively by the third party identified within the frame. In addition, any web page on which such information is collected is operated by the third party displayed on such page, not by PriceQuotes.com.

Personal information submitted to PriceQuotes.com via home improvement estimate-request forms is stored in a secure, protected location, and is managed privately within the PriceQuotes.com website, to be referred exclusively to pre-screened third parties who are directly capable of fulfilling your estimate-request in the area in which you live.

PriceQuotes.com, however, is not responsible for the information collection and use practices of these third parties and we recommend that you refer to the privacy policy of each third party company. If you do not want your information to be handled by these third parties, you can choose not to allow the collection of information by not using a particular service or by not providing any information at that time.

**Does PriceQuotes.com use cookies or track IP Addresses?**

A "cookie" is a small bit of record-keeping information that many Web sites store on a user's computer. A cookie can only be used by the site which placed it and is usually used to identify session information and preferences or to let the site know you have been there before and save you time reentering usernames, passwords, and other information. How long the cookie exists on your computer is set by the site placing the cookie, though you can remove them yourself at any time.

When a user visits PriceQuotes.com, an anonymous cookie is placed on the user's hard drive, and exists for only the time the browser is open. This cookie contains no contact information and is used exclusively to facilitate your navigation of our site and to keep track of your preferences during a particular session only. The cookie is not linked to your contact information at any time.

An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet.

PriceQuotes.com also records IP (Internet Protocol) addresses. We use the data only for statistical purposes in counting distinct users and identifying fraud attempts in our advertising.

We use the services of Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use the site. To do this, Google Analytics uses cookies to assist in the analysis of the sites' traffic, audience and usability. This information helps us understand which pages are most attractive to our visitors, how our site is being used and what kinds of information our customers prefer.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information on our website. These companies may use information (not including personal information such as your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to our website in order to provide advertisements on our website and other websites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp) If you would like to see what non-identifying information one of these companies has collected about your internet usage, please click [here.](http://www.bluekai.com/registryoverview.html)

**Can I choose how my personal information is used?**

**Estimate-Request Forms**  
If you submit an estimate-request for a home-improvement project to PriceQuotes.com, and then decide that you would like to cancel your request, you may opt-out by contacting us through our contact page, and we will be happy to honor your request. However, please note, PriceQuotes.com often establishes contacts for estimate-requests within a 24 hour period. If you want to opt-out of your estimate-request after you have been contacted by one of our pre-screened home improvement business partners, you will need to make your request directly to the business itself. PriceQuotes.com is not responsible for the opt-out policies of these businesses.

**Email Correspondence**  
If you send PriceQuotes.com an email, and do not want PriceQuotes.com to reply to your question or comment, you may opt-out from receiving a response by contacting us through our contact page and we will be happy to honor your request.

**How do I access my personal information?**

If you wish to correct personal information submitted to us via an estimate-request form or email so that we may successfully respond to your request, question or comment, please contact us through our contact page providing us with the correct information.

**Does PriceQuotes.com collect personal information from children under 13?**

PriceQuotes.com does not intend, and the site is not designed or marketed, to collect personal information from children under 13, including personal information submitted to us via email. We recognize a special obligation to protect personal information obtained from young children. We urge parents to instruct their children to never give out their real names, addresses, or phone numbers, without permission, when on-line. No information should be submitted to PriceQuotes.com, whether via the site or in the form of email correspondence, by children 12 and under.

**What safeguards does PriceQuotes.com use to protect my personal information?**

**Purchase-Request Forms**  
PriceQuotes.com only stores and uses personal information submitted voluntarily through purchase-request forms for the purpose of directing those requests to established, pre-screened business partners. When submitted electronically, this information is accepted and securely stored internally and exclusively within the PriceQuotes.com website. Such information is delivered to personnel within the PriceQuotes.com company, who maintain the highest level of confidentiality, and is subsequently referred exclusively to the business partners who are able to fulfill the estimate-request. Personal information submitted through these forms is not knowingly made available to the general public, including unsolicited third parties. The information is likewise never accumulated to be sold at large by PriceQuotes.com to multiple third parties for general marketing or any other purpose.

**Surveys**  
Occasionally we may conduct visitor surveys to better serve our audience or for the benefit of third parties with whom we do business. The general results may then be shared with our partners. We will not share any information about individuals or their specific responses with any third party unless that individual consents.

**Email Correspondence**  
PriceQuotes.com maintains appropriate safeguards to ensure the security and privacy of the information you provide us via email by destroying such information within 30 days of its receipt.

Because PriceQuotes.com does not store or use any personal information about its visitors other than for the purposes stated in this privacy policy, PriceQuotes.com does not have any mechanisms in place to ensure data quality, such as the accuracy of information submitted by visitors directly to our site.

**How do I ask a question or file a complaint?**

Any questions or complaints about PriceQuotes.com or this privacy statement can be resolved by contacting PriceQuotes.com through our contact page.

**Changes or Revisions to This Policy**

If we are going to use your personal information in a manner different from that stated in this Policy at the time of collection, we will notify you via email. You will be given a choice as to whether or not to allow us to use your information in this different manner.
